Guide to the Juris Hartmanis papers, 1965-2008.
Hartmanis, Juris papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Juris Hartmanis papers, 1965-2008.
16-13-3786
Juris Hartmanis
21 cubic feet.
Correspondence, Publications, Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes publications by Hartmanis and others in the field of computer science, correspondence, and subject files.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Emeritus professor of Computer Science, Cornell University.
Hartmanis was born in Latvia, received his Bachelor's degree from the University of Marburg in Germany, his Master's degree in Applied Mathematics from the University of Kansas City in 1951, and his Ph.D. in Mathematics from the California Institute of Technology in 1955. After teaching at Cornell and Ohio State, he joined the General Electric Research Laboratory in 1958, where he developed principles of computational complexity theory. In 1965 he became a professor at Cornell and was on of the founders and first chairman of its computer science department. In 1993, he won the Turing Award along with Richard Stearns.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes publications by Hartmanis and others in the field of computer science, correspondence, and subject files.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Hartmanis, Juris; College of Engineering.Dept. of Computer Science.; Cornell University--Faculty.
Subjects:
Computer science; Machine theory; Computational complexity
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Additional material and digital versions can be found online here: http://ecommons.cornell.edu/handle/1813/14935
SERIES LIST
Series I. Papers by Various Computer Scientists
Boxes 1-7; Box 8- Folders: 1-59
Series II. Reprints - Hartmanis
Box 9- Folders: 1-66
Series III. Course Material
Box 9- Folders: 66-88; Box 10- Folders: 1-9
Series IV. Correspondence
Box 10- Folders: 10-20, 27-37; Box 11- Folder: 10
Series V. Lecture and Subject Files
Box 10- Folders: 38-44; Box 11- Folders: 7-9, 11-50
Series VI. Department of Computer Science Material
Box 10- Folders: 21-26; Box 21
Series VII. National Science Foundation (NSF) Grant Material
Box 10- Folders: 45-47; Box 11- Folders: 1-6, 43, 47; Box 18
Series VIII. Other Professional Material
Boxes 11-20
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Papers By Various Computer Scientists
  - Adachi, A. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Adachi, A. and T. Kasai (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Akers, S. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Akkoyunlu, E., A. Bernstein, and R. Schantz (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allen, D. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alton, Donald A. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alton, Donald A. and E. W. Madison (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Amar, V. and G. Putzolu (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Amoroso, S. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Allender, E. W. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Angluin, D. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Apostolico, A. and A. S. Fraenkel (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Arbib, M. A. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Ausiello, G. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Babai, L. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bauer, F. L. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Baer, R. M. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Baker, B. S. and R. V. Book (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Baker, T. P. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bakker, J. W. and W. P. deRoever (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Balcazar, J. L. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Banerju, R. B. and G. W. Ernst (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Baron, R. J. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Barzdin, J. M. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Barzdin, J. M. and Riga Co. Papers (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bass, L. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Bavel, Zamir (Box 1, Folder 26A)
  - Beatty, J. C. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Becvar, J. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Beigel, R. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bennett, C. H. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Benson, David B. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Berman, L. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Berman, P. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Bibel, W. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bilardi, G. (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Bishop, Errett (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Biskup, J. (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Biswas, S. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Blattner, M. (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Blikle, A. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Bloom, S. L. (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Blum, L. and M. Blum (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Blum, M. (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Bohm, C. (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Book, Ronald V. (1) (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Book, Ronald V. (2) (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Book, Ronald V. (3) (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Boone, W. W. and G. Higman (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Bork, A. (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Borodin, A. (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Borodin, A. and A. Demers (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Brandstadt, Von A. and D. Saalfeld (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Breidbart, S. I. (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Bremermann, Hans (Box 1, Folder 53A)
  - Braunmuhl, B. von and R. Verbeek (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Brooks, H. (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Buchberger, B. (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Buchi, J. Richard (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Burks, A. W. (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Budach, L. (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Cai, Jin-yi (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Carr, John W. III (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Case, John (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Chaitin, G. J. (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Chandra, A. K. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Chen, Keh-Jiann (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cherniavsky, J. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Chytil, M. P. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Cobham, A. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cole, Steven N. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Coleman, T. F. and C. Hempel (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Constable, R. L. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Cook, Steven A. (1) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cook, Steven A. (2) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Corrada, Manuel C. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Crossley, John N. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Cudia, D. F. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Culik, Karel (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Daley, Robert (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Dassow, Von Jurgen (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Davida, G. I. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - De Bakker, J. W. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - De Luca, A. and F. Adrianopoli (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Demers, A. and J. Donahue (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Dennis, J. B. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Deussen, P. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Dijkstra, E. W. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Dilger, E. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Dill, F. H. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Dobkin, D. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Dowd, M. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Downey, R. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Dymond, P. W. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Ecker, Von K. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Ehrenfeucht, A. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Eichner, L. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Eilenberg, S. and J. B. Wright (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Elgot, Calvin C. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - van Emde Boas, P. (1) (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - van Emde Boas, P. (2) (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Engeler, E. (1) (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Engeler, E. (2) (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Epstein, G. (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Ernest, G. W. (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Erni, W. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Evans, T. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Ewald, R., B. Buzbee, and J. Worlton (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Feigenbaum, J. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Feldman, E. D. and J. C. Owings Jr. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Feldman, J. A. (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Fenner, Stephen A. (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Fenstad, J. E. (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Feynman, Richard P. (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Fischer, M. J. and M. S. Paterson (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Fischer, M. J. (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Fischer, P. C. (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Fleck, A. C. and R. S. Limaye (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Floyd, R. W. (1) (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Floyd, R. W. (2) (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Fortune, S. (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Freivalds, R. (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Friedman, D. P. and D. S. Wise (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Friedman, E. P. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Friedman, H. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Furst, M., J. Saxe, and M. Sipser (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Gacs, Peter (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Galil, Zvi (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Galligo, A. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Ganesan, K. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Garzon, M. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Gasrarch, William I. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Geffert, V. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Gill, John (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Ginsburg, S. (1) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Ginsburg, S. (2) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Godel, K. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Goguen, J. A. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Goldberg, M. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Goldschlager, L. M. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Goldsmith, J. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Goldstine, J. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Gordon, D. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Gorn, S. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Grefenstette, J. J. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Greibach, Sheila (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Gries, D. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Grigor'ev, D. Ju. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Gruska, J. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Gupta, S. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Gurevich, Y. (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous G - Russian Papers (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Hajek, P. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Hamlet, R. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Han, Xioafeng (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Hanak, J. (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Hansen, Per Brinch (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Harel, D. (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Harju, T. (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Harrison, Michael A. (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Hart, Johnson M. (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Havel, I. M. (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Heller, H. (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Hamachandra, L. (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Hennie, F. C. (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Herman, G. T. (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Hibbard, T. N. (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Hirschfelder, J. J. (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Hoare, C. A. R. and P. E. Lauer (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Hodgson, B. R. and C. F. Kent (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Holt, Richard C. (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Homer, S. (1) (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Homer, S. (2) (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Hopcroft, J. E. (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Hopfield, J. J. (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Horvath, S., et al. (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Hotz, G. (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Hromkovic, J. (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Hunt, Harry B. (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Ibarra, Oscar H. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Igarashi, Y. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Ierardi, D. (1) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Ierardi, D. (2) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Ierardi, D. (3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Indermark, Klaus (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Information Processing - IFIP 9th World Computer Congress, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Ito, T. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Jain, S. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Jantzen, M. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Jia-Wei, Hong (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Johnson, David S. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Johnson, Donald B. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Jones, Neil D. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Kameda, T. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Kamin, S. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Kannan, R. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Kaplan, Donald M. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Kasai, T. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Katajainen, J. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Ker-I Ko (1) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Ker-I Ko (2) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Ker-I Ko (3) (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Kidson, D. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Kinber, E. B. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Kinber, J. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Kintala, C. M. R. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Kirsig, B. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Klarner, D. A. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Knuth, Donald E. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Kobayashi, K. (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Komogorov, A. N. (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Korenjak, A. J. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Korshunov, A. D. (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Kosaraju, S. Rao (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Kozen, Dexter (1) (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Kozen, Dexter (2) (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Kozen, Dexter (3) (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Krause, Matthias (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Kuck, Conrad (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Kumar, Vipin (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Kuroda, S-Y (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Kurtz, S. A. (1) (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Kurtz, S. A. (2) (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Kurtz, S. A. (3) (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Kutylowski, M. (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Ladner, Richard E. (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Laing, Richard A. (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Landau, S. (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Landweber, L. H. (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Langmaack, Hans (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Lauer, P. (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Lax, Peter D. (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Lawler, E. L. (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Lee, John A. N. (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Lee, K. P. (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Leivant, D. (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Leggett, Ernest W. (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - van Leeuwen, Jan (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Lenat, Douglas B. (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Levin, L. A. (1) (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Levin, L. A. (2) (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Lewis, F. D. (1) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Lewis, F. D. (2) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Lewis, Philip (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Li, M. and C. Bajaj (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Li, M. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Lighthill, Prof. Sir James (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Lipton, Richard J. (1) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Lipton, Richard J. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Lischke, G. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Liu, C. L. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Long, T. J. (1) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Long, T. J. (2) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Long, T. J. (3) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Loui, Michael C. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Loveland, D. W. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Luks, Eugene M. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Lutz, J. H. (1) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Lutz, J. H. (2) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Lynch, Nancy A. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Lyndon, Roger C. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous L - AFL Notes (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Maass, Wolfgang (1) (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Maass, Wolfgang (2) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Maass, Wolfgang (3) (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Machtey, Michael (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - MacLane, Saunders (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Mahaney, Stephen (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Manna, Zohar (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Maurer, H. A. (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Mazurkiewicz, Antoni (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - McCarthy, John (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - McCreight, Edward M. (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - McNaughton, Robert (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Meer, K. (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Mehlhorn, Kurt (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Melville, Robert (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Meseguer, J. (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Meyer, A. R. (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Mezei, J. (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Micali, Silvio (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Mikotajczak, Bolestaw (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Miller, Gary L. (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - deMillo, Richard A. (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Minsky, Marvin (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Miyano, S. (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Mohrherr, Jeanleah (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Monien, Burkhard (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Moore, Daniel (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Moravek, Jaroslav (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Mukhopadhyay, Amar (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Miscellaneous M - Handwritten Notes (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Nemeti, I. (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Neumann, P. G. (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Newell, Allen (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Nicklas, B. M. (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Nicolis, John S. (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Noe, Philip S. (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Nozaki, A. (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - O'Donnell, Michael (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Ogden, W. F. (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Ogiwara, M. (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Owicki, Susan Speer (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Pager, David (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Pan, V. Ya. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Papadimitriou, C. H. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Parberry, Ian (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Park, David (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Parnas, D. L. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Paterson, Michael S. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Penttonen, Martti (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Peterson, G. L. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Petri, C. A. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Pfluger, J., and P. Ochsenschlager (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Pickett, H. E. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Pinter, Charles (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Pippenger, Nicholas (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Pitt, Leonard (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Plaisted, David A. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Pomerance, Carl (Box 6, Folder 16a)
  - Pour-El, M. B., and I. Richards (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Pratt, V. R. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Probert, Robert L. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Pudlak, P., and J. Tuma (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Putzolu, G. R. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Rahimi, M. A. (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Ratner, D. H. (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Ravikumar, B. (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Reckhow, Robert A. (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Regan, Kenneth W. (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Reiss, Steven P. (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Reps, Thomas (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Reusch, Brend (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Reynolds, John C. (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Richardson, D. (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Ritchie, G. D. (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Rivest, Ronald (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Robertson, E. L. (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Rogers, Hartley (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Rosen, Barry K. (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Rosenberg, Arnold L. (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Rosenkrantz, Daniel J. (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Rota, Gian-Carlo (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Rothstein, Jerome (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Royer, James S. (1) (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Royer, James S. (2) (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Royer, James S. (3) (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Ruby, S. S. (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Rutledge, J. D. (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Sachse-Akerlind, D. (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Salomaa, A., and M. Steinby (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Salton, G. (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Santa Barbara, CA - Conference on Computation Complexity Theory, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Savage, J. E. (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Savitch, Walter J. (1) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Savitch, Walter J. (2) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Scarpellini, B. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Schenhage, A. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Schinzel, B. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Schmidt, Erik Meineche (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Schneider, H. J., and H. Ehrig (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Schnorr, C. P. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Schonhage, A. and V. Strassen (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Schoning, U. (1) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Schoning, U. (2) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Schreiber, P. P. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Schwartz, Steven Thomas (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Scott, Dana (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Helmut, Seidl (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Seiferas, Joel I. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Selman, A. L. (1) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Selman, A. L. (2) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Shamir, E. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Shank, H. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Shepherdson, J. C. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Siefkes, D. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Simon, Istvan (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Simon, J. (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Simovici, D. A., and S. Istrail (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Sipser, M. (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Skowron, A. (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Slisenko, A. O. (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Smith, Carl (1) (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Smith, Carl (2) (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Smith, Carl (3) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Smolensky, Roman (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Soare, R. I. (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Solomon, M. K. (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Solovay, R. M. (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Springsteel, Fred Neil (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Stearns, R. E. (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Stockmeyer, L. J. (1) (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Stockmeyer, L. J. (2) (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Story, James R. (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Strang, Gilbert (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Strassen, V. (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Strnad, Pavel (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Sudborough, I. H. (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Synmanski, T. G. (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Szabo, M. E. (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Szepietowski, A. (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Tanaka, E. (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Tarjan, R. E. (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Teitelbaum, R. T. (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Thatcher, J. W. (1) (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Thatcher, J. W. (2) (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Thompson, C. D. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Thurow, Lester C. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Toda, S. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Toshio, Nomura (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Trakhtenbrot, B. A. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Traub, J. F. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Traub, R. E. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Turing, A. M. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Valiant, L. G. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Verbeek, R. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Vishkin, U. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Vitanyi, Paul M. B., and B. Awerbuch (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Vizirani, V. V. (1) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Vizirani, V. V. (2) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Wagner, Klaus W. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Walk, K. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Wand, M. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Wang, Hao, and B. Dunham (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Wang, Jie (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Watanabe, Osamu (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Wegner, Peter (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Weicker, R. (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Weihrauch, K. (1) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Weihrauch, K. (2) (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Weber, Andreas (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Wershulz, Arthur G. (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Wilson, Christopher (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Winkler, Peter (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Wise, D. S. (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Wolfram, S. (1) (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Wolfram, S. (2) (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Wotschke, D. (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Wozniakowski, H. (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Wrathall, C. (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Yao, Andrew C. (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Yeh, R. T. (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Yesha, Y. (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Young, Paul (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Younger, D. H. (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Yu, C. T. (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Yunzeng, Wu (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Zachos, Stathis (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Zak, S. (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Zech, K-A. (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Zeigler, B. P. (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Zeigler, P. (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Zeigler, H. P. (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Zimand, Marius (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Historic Papers
  - Becvar, Jiri; Probleme der Komplexität in der Theorie der Algorithmen und Automaten (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Becvar, Jiri; Real-Time and Complexity Problems in Automata Theory (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Blum, Manuel; A Machine-Independent Theory of the Complexity of Recursive Functions (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Cobham, Alan; The Intrinsic Computational Difficulty (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Fischer, Patrick C.; Multi-Tape and Infinite-State Automata - A Survey (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Grzegorczyk, A.; Some Classes of Recursive Functions (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Hartmanis, J., and R. E. Stearns; On the Computational Complexity of Algorithms (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - McCarthy, J.; Towards a Mathematical Science of Computation (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - McCarthy, J.; A Basis for a Mathematical Theory of Computation, Preliminary Report (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Myhill, John; Linear Bounded Automata (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Rabin, Michael O.; Real Time Computation (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Rabin, Michael O.; Degree of Difficulty of Computing a Function and a Partial Ordering of Recursive Sets (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Ritchie, Robert W.; Classes of Predictably Computable Functions (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Yamada, Hisao; Real-Time Computation and Recursive Functions Not Real-Time Computable (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Series II. Reprints - Hartmanis
  - Memory Bounds for Recognition of Context-Free and Context-Sensitive Languages, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Hierarchies of Memory Limited Computations, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - On the Computational Complexity of Algorithms, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Two Tests for the Linearity of Sequential Machines, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Minimal Feedback Realizations of Sequential Machines, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Context-Free Languages and Turing Machine Computations, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Sets of Numbers Defined by Finite Automata, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Homomorphic Images of Linear Sequential Machines, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - On Memory Requirements for Context-Free Language Recognition, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Tape-Reversal Bounded Turing Machine Computations, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - On the Recognition of Primes by Automata, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Computational Complexity of One-Tape Turing Machine Computations, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Automata-Based Computational Complexity, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - On the Complexity of Undecidable Problems in Automata Theory, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Two Memory Bounds for the Recognition of Primes by Automata, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - What Makes Some Language Theory Problems Undecidable, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - A Note on One-Way and Two-Way Automata, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - On Non-Determinacy in Simple Computing Devices, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Size Arguments in the Study of Computation Speeds, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - The Use of Lists in the Study of Undecidable Problems in Automata Theory, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Computational Complexity of Random Access Stored Program Machines, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - An Overview of the Theory of Computational Complexity, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Group Theoretic Characterization of Linear Permutation Automata, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Computational Complexity of Formal Translations, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - The LBA Problem and Its Importance in the Theory of Computing, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - A Note on Tape Bounds for SLA Language Processing, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - On Simple Goedel Numberings and Translations, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - On Tape Bounds for Single Letter Alphabet Language Processing, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Generalized Kolmogorov Complexity and the Structure of Feasible Computations, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 29)